Welcome to module one. In this module, which is very introductory, we're going to be talking about the college expectations that you may not have figured out, you know, doing your own research.
So I'd like to say that in this module, it's very, it's very straightforward for navigating college, the four unwritten rules that I will be mentioning, but, you know, read the syllabus, it has everything in it.
It has your instructor's office hours, it has virtually everything that you need dates, times when things are due. What I like to do is I just write them down and set reminders for myself when different projects are due.
You know, utilize office hours, extremely important to have not a lot of college students utilize office hours. And I think it's really necessary to not just, you know, get rid of the confusion that you have about the course, but it's also a great way to connect with your, your instructor.
They could serve as a possible recommendation for you down the line. So it's great to go to the office hours.
E-mailing. E-mailing is, is crucial. You aren't emailing your friends. You aren't emailing a high school teacher. You're emailing a, an academic professional in college.
Yeah, you're not emailing your friends, right? You, there's, there's specific email pros you have that professional and it just takes you a long way. You can, you can also email, you know, career professionals. It'll take you a long way.
And then, finally, ask before you collaborate.
I know a lot of colleges have these rules on, on making sure you don't have, you know, academic dishonesty violations and plagiarism.
And it may be fun to work on a project with your friend who's in the same class, but if the syllabus or the professor doesn't allow it, it could be considered plagiarism.
Or if you had a college assignment that you had in another course and in a specific course or another course down the line, you realize you already wrote a topic about it previously and you turn in the same essay.
That's also considered plagiarism, believe it or not. I've had to really dissect that on my own because I didn't know as well.
But, yeah, these are there, there are multiple different rules of college, but, you know, read the assignments, read the lessons activities.
There will be a full thorough breakdown on it. And make sure you take note of, of, of what's important, especially by reading the syllabus. I hope you read my syllabus. Okay.